Guide to the Brooklyn Division of the Protestant Council of Churches records ARC.270
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 5: Subject files, 1950-1974
  - Twin Pines: Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - Twin Pines Committee: Education Task Force, 1970-1971 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - United Farm Workers, 1972 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - Borough Assembly, 1973 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - Brooklyn Clerical Union, 1973 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - Brooklyn Heights Ministerial Association, 1973 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - Brownsville, 1973 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - Bushwick Ecumenial Parish Association, 1973 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - Christian Help in Park Slope, 1973 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - Church Women United, 1973 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - Clergy Concerned About a Better Fort Greene, 1973 (Box ARC.270 19 of 36)
  - Clergy Volunteer Program, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Board of Directors, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Education Committee, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Executive Committee, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Executive program staff, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Executive secretary - C. Straut, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Finance Committee - Memos, agenda, minutes, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Finance Committee - Brooklyn Church and Mission Federation, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Flatbush Church Community Association, [1973] (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Flatlands Ecumenical Committee, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Fundraising Committee: Minutes, memos, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Inter-religious Coalition of NY Clergy, [1973] (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Local Ecumenism Committee, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Local Ecumenism Committee - Christian Relations Committee, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Board of Managers, [1973] (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Newsclippings, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Newsletters, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Nominating Committee, 1973 (Box ARC.270 20 of 36)
  - Park Slope Clergy Association, 1973 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Pastoral Care Committee, 1973 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Planning Committee, 1973 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Political Issues, 1973 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - St. Paul's United Methodist Church, 1973 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - South Brooklyn Clergy Association, 1973 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Testimonial Dinner, 1973 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - United Farm Workers, 1973 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Bethany Deaconess Society, 1974 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Board of Managers, 1974 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Borough Assembly, 1974 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Brooklyn Clerical Union, 1974 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Bushwick Ecumenial Parish, [1974] (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Church Women United, 1974 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Citizens Urban Information Centers, 1974 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Clergy Concerned for a Better Fort Greene, 1974 (Box ARC.270 21 of 36)
  - Clergy Volunteer Program, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Contemporary Social Issues Committee, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Correspondence - In, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Correspondence - Out, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Development and Publica Relations Committee, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Education Committee, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Executive Committee, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Executive staff, 1973-1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Family Court Task Force, 1973-1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Finance Committee, 1974-1975 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Flatbush Church Community Association, 1973-1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Flatlands Ecumenical Committee, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - General Assembly, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Greenpoint, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Local Ecumenism Committee, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Newsclippings, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Newsletter, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - "No Place in the Sun" [sheet music of hymn by Charles Straut], [circa 1960s-1970s] (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Park Slope Clergy Association, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Pastoral Care Committee, [1974] (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Planning Committee, [1974] (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Political Issues, [1974] (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - Press releases, 1974 (Box ARC.270 22 of 36)
  - St. Paul's United Methodist Church, 1973-1974 (Box ARC.270 23 of 36)
  - St. Paul's United Methodist Church - "For growth…for Christ", 1974 (Box ARC.270 23 of 36)
  - Testimonial Dinner - Correspondence and misc., 1974 (Box ARC.270 23 of 36)
  - Testimonial Dinner - Publications and newsclips, 1974 (Box ARC.270 23 of 36)
  - United Farm Workers, 1974 (Box ARC.270 23 of 36)
- Series 6: Scrapbooks, 1847-1864, 1934-1964 (Box ARC.270 23 of 36, Box ARC.270 24 of 36, Box ARC.270 25 of 36, Box ARC.270 26 of 36, Box ARC.270 27 of 36, Box ARC.270 28 of 36, Box ARC.270 36 of 36)
  These scrapbooks contain newspaper clippings and photographs regarding the Brooklyn Division's activities and current events of interest to the organization. The newspaper clippings also detail the activities of many individual Protestant parishes within Brooklyn. Additionally, the series contains photocopies of Grace Church Vestry minutes from 1847 to 1864.
- Series 7: Photographs, circa 1900-1974 (Box ARC.270 28 of 36, Box ARC.270 35 of 36, Box ARC.270 36 of 36)
  The photographs in this series document the Brooklyn Division's events and gatherings, most notably its testimonial dinners.